[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Cobras are venomous snakes of family Elapidae, that generally inhabit regions of these two continents.", "correct_answer": "Asia and Africa", "incorrect_answers": ["South America and Asia", "Asia and Australia", "South America and Australia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Contrary to this celestial bodys true nature, the term asteroid means what according to its greek origins?", "correct_answer": "Star-like", "incorrect_answers": ["Cone-shaped", "Planet-like", "Drifting freely"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Mortimer finds out towards the end of the movie Arsenic and Old Lace that he really isnt a Brewster.  Who is his father?", "correct_answer": "Sea Cook", "incorrect_answers": ["Mr. Harper", "Sea Captain", "Mr. Witherspoon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What artist wrote and performed the song Tears in Heaven?", "correct_answer": "Eric Clapton", "incorrect_answers": ["Billie Holiday", "Duke Ellington", "Billy Joel"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the B vitamins is also known as folic acid?", "correct_answer": "Vitamin B9", "incorrect_answers": ["Vitamin B1", "Vitamin B12", "Vitamin B5"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How much does Carl Codys airline ticket to San Francisco cost, and what airline is it on?", "correct_answer": "$45.00, one way -Continenetal Airlines", "incorrect_answers": ["36.00 round trip - Pacific Southwest Airlines", "29.00 one way - Southwest Airlines, but only from Burbank!", "$55.00 one way - Shuttle by United"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Fill in the missing letter in this chain that has to do with the Solar System we live in: M, V, E, M, J, _, U, N.", "correct_answer": "S", "incorrect_answers": ["R", "P", "B"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of fish contains the valuable Omega-3 fatty acids, proven to fight depression and improve overall health?", "correct_answer": "Cold-water fish", "incorrect_answers": ["Marine fish", "Bony fish", "Cartilaginous fish"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 1996 musical movie co-written by Oliver Stone set a Guinness World Record for Most costume changes in a film?", "correct_answer": "Evita", "incorrect_answers": ["Hair", "Moulin Rouge", "Chicago"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who invented the first working television system?", "correct_answer": "John Logie Baird", "incorrect_answers": ["Thomas Edison", "Alexander Graham Bell", "Benjamin Franklin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the Don who controlled Little Italy when Vito Corleone was younger?", "correct_answer": "Don Fanucci", "incorrect_answers": ["Don Andolini", "Don Ciccio", "Don Carlito"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the full name of the Benetton fashion brand?", "correct_answer": "United Colors of Benetton", "incorrect_answers": ["United Benetton Designers", "Benetton Fashion Union", "Benetton Union"]}]